Jinsong Liu

Product Design

I am a designer with three years of work experience and a passion for user experience design, typography, and creative coding. I love articulating the "why" and "how" behind the creative process, and critically reflecting on the relationship between human and technology.

justsoyeah@gmail.com

\(+86 156 2231 9121

https://sylvesterlau.com

in Jinsong (Sylvester) Liu

Employment

Nov. 2018 - Jul. 2019, Guangzhou, China

Lead Product Designer / Runwise Co.

- Led the design of a consulting project for Kungfu Restaurant Co., presented design proposal and strategies to the client.
- Created UX design on Kungfu Order from the ground up, including research, prototyping, design and usability test.
 Worked closely with product managers to refine features and user flows in iterations.
- Designed interfaces and interaction for apps and dashboard, delivered and maintained a design system.

Jul. 2017 - Nov. 2018, Guangzhou, China

Product Designer / Runwise Co.

- Designed interface for Refuel App. Collaborated with product managers, editors and developers to launch the product.
- Designed illustrations for micro-course content.
- Contributed to user research and CMS design.

Jun. 2016 - Dec. 2016, Guangzhou, China

Interaction Designer Intern / ETU Design

- Assisted senior designers to design interface and user flow for the clients. Handed off design specs, measurement and document to engineers.
- Clients: China Mobile HK, China Merchants Bank, Pingan Bank

Education

Oct. 2020 - Dec. 2021

User Experience Design, MA

University of the Arts London

Jul. 2013 - Sep. 2017

Industrial Design, BE

Guangdong University of Technology

Awards

"WeChat Power" Annual Digital Service Award, 2018

Team Award / Nov. 2018

Best Engaged Employee of the Year

At Runwise Co. / Dec. 2018

Lauguage

English: IELTS 7.5

Mandarin: Native Speaker
Cantonese: Native Speaker